ROHAN… ADDS 30 CHIPS
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
EPISODE 28
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 1
ROHAN KISHIBE'S HOUSE: HALF BURNED
7,000,000 YEN IN FIRE DAMAGE
JOSUKE MAY HAVE ESCAPED UNSCATHED,
BUT HE MANAGED TO GET
EVEN FURTHER ON ROHAN'S BAD SIDE.
KAWAJIRI KOSAKU
SHINOBU
HAYATO
MIKITAKA HAZEKURA…
ALIEN OR STAND USER?!
MORIOH LANDMARK 8
"FUTATSUMORI TUNNEL"
COMPLETED IN THE YEAR KAEI 5 (1852),
AND RESTORED IN SHOWA 28,
THE TUNNEL STRETCHES SOME
450 METERS LONG AND
CONNECTS S CITY WITH MORIOH.
ITS CURVED LAYOUT OBSCURES
THE EXIT FROM THE ENTRANCE,
AND ITS LACK OF LIGHT HAS BEEN
THE CAUSE OF NUMEROUS ACCIDENTS.
MOST OF THE AREA'S YOUNGER
POPULATION THINK IT'S HAUNTED.
FUTATSUMORI
TUNNEL
CRASH
SMASH
CRUSH
YOUR BODY WILL FLY
BACKWARDS AT 70 km/h!
EPISODE 29
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 2